what's up champ what's up man how you
doing man how you do see you good to see
you back in the United States yes
excited happy the fight gets announced
like what's your initial
thought fights announced honestly I know
like five six months ago it's going to
be it's going to be I'm going to fight
with Arman because he's a number one
Contender right now and uh he really
deserve to fight for the title yeah
going back to your last fight a little
bit when you got done with the Dustin
porier fight and he was praised for
doing so well were you a little bit like
taking back by it because you ultimately
won four rounds and then submitted him
but it's almost like he had won because
he defended takedowns yeah yeah honestly
Dustin improve his wrestling game a lot
because always you have the trouble is
the wrestling fighters who have good
skills wrestling skills that's why I
think he did uh good job in the camp he
improved his defense and he gave me hard
time it was hard yes it was hard but
it's very good fight for defense and big
experience for mes yeah you think you
think you get judged a little
differently than most Fighters because
of how dominant you've been because
think about this right when I list your
last four it's finish Ola finish fol
kanowski finish volkanovski finish
Dustin porier but the fight against
Dustin porier felt like it was like 48
47 at least to the general public right
because he was doing things that we
hadn't seen many do against you do you
think that you get judged on a different
scale than most Fighters because of the
expectation of what you're going to do
to people no because they expect I will
like smash or like you know that's why
that we have Lara talk about after the
first fight against wowski and that
fight that the last fight I think
everybody expect I smash Dustin but this
guy is a high level fighter it's not not
easy to finish someone you know but in
the press conference we have good
discuss he say I will make you sleep I
will KN knock you out but I will I told
him I was told him if you're not tap I
will make you sleep you know and I
finish him in the last round but he T
and sleep he never fell asleep he sleep
he fell asleep too yes yes watch I don't
think so man I think he tapped but I
don't think he fell asleep watch watch
okay I'll go back for a couple of second
he really yes so Arman suia he's
fighting Charles Ola you watch yeah what
did you think how much improvement has
this man made since you guys fought the
first time of course he improved he have
more experience but same skills you know
he he beat the all all this guy because
they don't have wrestling but when
someone have good wrestling skills he
always have trouble with gamr with me
and it's going to be again he have good
wring skill but if somebody defends they
have problem go back to that first fight
in Russia right you guys are fighting
you beat him
3027 3027
2928 this has been universally called
the toughest fight that you've had in
your entire career but you I'm just
trying to tell you just watch fight
with I have watched the fight but the
idea is based on that fight this is why
this is the toughest opponent of your
career it was one of the hard fight of
course but it's not like toughest fight
because the five round with volkanovski
it was crazy it was hard rate more than
200 it's SC you know but maybe I was
underestimating because he's a short
notice short notice nobody know him and
he don't have name you know and I never
watch his f fight and uh he did well in
that fight but I like to finish the old
questions you know when I have with wosi
the fight I told everybody I have to
close the close the I have to the finish
the questions and finish you know that's
why next the second fight I will be
looking for the finish and make
everybody shut up so so here's one thing
right one of the things you just said
maybe I underestimated him first fight
you said you kind of like underestimated
volkanovski a little bit when we talked
about the wrestling you would laugh you
would laugh when we spoke about him
being able to wrestle and all that and
ultimately that presented a few issues
do you have to earn does somebody have
to earn your respect before you respect
them so to fight the second time will
always be hard honestly I like to fight
second time because you know not I don't
like REM much but you know when I fought
second time I know everything what my
opponent can do and it's not going to be
surprise for me you know but sometimes
when somebody like Dustin did defense
wrestling and they like defends my
ambition skill you know it's a little
bit surprised me but when I know
everything what my opponent will do and
you know I have more more options when
you think back to that first fight what
can you point to that you think might
have been surprising right what did he
do in that fight to make it one of the
tougher fights in your career same
things I don't know he's where he I
think he took you out he took me down
three times no one times
man no no no watch the fight you never
watch my fight I watch your fights all
the time okay watch three times nobody
brother even you you cannot take me down
three times brother taking you down
three times many many times no no it's
not true you know the first fight and I
don't know his background you know he
defends my wrestling he give me just you
know he's tough that's why he give me
hard time but now I know everything what
he can do so you think you finish it I
think
yes you know Charles every round almost
finish him do some giltin do some
triangle choke like everything very
close but I think I have more chance
it's been a while since you fought what
has the champion been what have you been
to like what have you been doing how
have you improved in the gym since the
last time you you know man I training
really hard every Camp every time
nonstop that's why I always improve I
still improving right now and I love to
fight and you know now it's my goal to
finish all questions what's the
expectation for this second fight in
this regard right you fought him before
he has been very vocal that he can fight
you he can beat you he doesn't hide that
he wants to go and wrestle and take you
down is it just about winning and
proving or do you have to kind of let
the entire division know that there is
more separation than even they even
imagine in terms of where you are
opposed to them uh right now in 155
pounds uh you know let's a little bit
talk about Arman honestly I told all my
fight career I want to fight this real
Contender or this a real fighter who
deserve the title fight he is the tough
guy you know that's why I think he is
deserved and it's going to be huge fight
for defense because he have all skills
he all skills he good in the Striking he
good in the wrestling grappling that's
why it's going to be two high level
Fighter fights the fight against B daru
he finished him bad that was the first
time that we saw his power on display as
that time is Dar he just came back
shortly from the when ala beat him smash
him knock him out and the fighters some
of the fighters did mistake you know
like what wowski did with
stura somebody knocked them out and they
want to go back soon soon and show
people it's nothing it's I don't feel
nothing after The Knockout and what
Arman did with DAR what tapur did with
wos they just rush a little bit did
mistake we spoke a while back about you
wanting to fight in America fought in
New Jersey now you get to fight in
California what to be how excited are
you to be fighting at like at home
essentially right because you spent so
many years in California because I like
to fight in us because a lot of time I
fought in Abu Dhabi it's also it's my
second home you know but in us you know
I think it's more focused not many
people can come because the Visa problem
but I bring all my team now before 45
days I come to the US and I come to
Vegas we have here ufcp Lara gyms
sparing Partners everything for be ready
100% how many guys are here and what is
the camp going to look like being at
your CH fight for title and Omar's
fighting for title brother in the
weekend khabib will come khabib told me
he said he's here he told me to tell you
guys get ready yeah yeah he told group
send message to the group guys be ready
nice mon ni smash you guys yes maybe you
can come join for us just control him a
little bit because he don't listen I
always tell you a head coach you older
than him stop him no he is just a
psychopath nobody can control him come
maybe you I can't control it you know I
can't try try Jo to the camp man I'll
come by but I can't control this it's
going to be also very good for you
brother lose weight hey you know we got
stop talking about my weight cuz you
look like you put on a few pounds no
brother you look heavy
180 180 and you fight 155 yes weight
bully this is what you are so you beat
Arman suian and you've defended this
title on so many different occasions now
right what's next I don't know if I
looking behind Arman if I beat him I
don't know I'm tired to give somebody
very much you know I need the
second belt below there we'll see lot of
good fighters in Charles has show right
again that he's right back in the
mix man I beat him Arman beat
him it's nothing excited you know to
beat him again but if he want if Dana
want if friend want why not yeah again I
can beat him so training here in Las
Vegas 45 days
you've already started I'd imagine
getting prepared getting ready back in
dagistan how long have you been focusing
before getting to America to make sure
that you're ready going to be ready on
January you know I start my Camp before
three months I start in Mahala and we go
to the mountain time and go back to
mahaj kalala and we come us now but all
years are training every day doesn't
matter where you go we have always close
with us to go
to wrestling 30 minutes 15 minutes like
every day is that going to be the focus
this camp like you going do a lot of
wrestling anybody specific you're
bringing to wrest which any High L wrest
I see you guys you're from dagistan no
you're from dagistan so clearly you guys
have great wrestlers you can grab a kid
off the street Dagan to come wrestl we
don't have to bring some special people
because all dagistan when they was born
they know how to wrestle true it's true
man you know this you send the kids from
dagistan Brother what happened they I
sent them to d stand because they needed
to be
pushed we we try to give him respect
invite him they're very good but when
they go life it's hard our kids hard
hard my Kids versus dagistan kids but
the genetics you know where the genetics
bro we have I have great kids they burn
and they focus to be Champion you do
this every time man we actually did
really well against you guys I respect I
respect your team resling what giloy Gil
Roy wrest Gilroy yeah yeah yes I saw
toir wearing a nice shirt the other day
Gilroy wrestling that's what I hey you
got me a shirt yes where in the car why
why didn't you bring it let's go brother
our house see drink te I have to work I
have to work all right man well you
about to fight Arman R for a second time
it's exciting tough fight you will be
there I will be there yeah yeah hey what
about Umar being on the title like how
what does that mean to you you and Omar
fighting the little boy now is fighting
for a championship on the same card as
you like that's got to be special no you
know Omar s he not in usfc you know like
many years ago he come with us to the
camp just help us to take care of the
house but it's a big guy now fight for
the
title dream comes true you know yeah
he's deserve he's a hard worker and it's
GNA be huge mat H H huge night for the
our team oh man well good luck champ
thank you thank can't wait to watch it
thank you always good to see you